The stock of a private insurance company may rise by 5%.
Dealers have made strong buying efforts
on the stock. Yatin Mota said that dealers are bullish in this market.
Dealers in the city of Russ have
advised to bet, that is, buy today and sell tomorrow.
Dealers feel that a rise of 3 to 4 percent is visible in this market.
Buying was seen in this market today from mutual funds. A
mood of recovery was seen in the market.
Nifty came out of the stock with a soft point
improvement while Bank Nifty improved by 200 points.
Nifty Midcap index rose for the seventh consecutive day.
Metal stocks saw a rise after China's rate cut.
Hind Copper was seen trading more than 2% higher. On
the other hand, good buying was seen in IT and auto stocks.
Tata Motors
reached a 7-year high. Here, after the block deal,
HDFC
became the top gainer in futures by making a big move.
In this market environment today,
dealers in the dealing room have placed bets on Russ and ICC Lombard.
According to the investigation of CNBC Awaaz's Yatin Mota, both the stocks  Dealers have
given buying advice to their clients.
Quoting sources from the dealing room, Yatin Mota
said that dealers have a bullish opinion in this city.
Dealers have also
advised to buy today and sell tomorrow in the city of Ras.
According to dealers, a rise of 3 to 5 percent is possible in this city.
Buying has been seen today by mutual funds in this city.
Analysts are keeping an eye on the insurance stocks of ICC Lombard.
Today, dealers have
placed a claim on the private sector Vim stock.
For good earnings, dealers have advised their
clients to buy in the city of ICC Lombard.
According to dealers, a rise of 3 to 5 percent is possible in this city.